[
  {
    "front": "regarder, voir, être visible",
    "back": "見"
  },
  {
    "front": "mettre dans, entrer",
    "back": "入"
  },
  {
    "front": "sortir, présenter",
    "back": "出"
  },
  {
    "front": "se reposer",
    "back": "休"
  },
  {
    "front": "aliment, nourriture, manger",
    "back": "食"
  },
  {
    "front": "parler, conversation, histoire",
    "back": "言"
  },
  {
    "front": "dehors, extérieur",
    "back": "外"
  },
  {
    "front": "pays",
    "back": "国"
  },
  {
    "front": "langue, mot, raconter",
    "back": "語"
  },
  {
    "front": "ami",
    "back": "友"
  }
]
